Here we are at Michael Freeman, programmer of pizza party, and we're going to do an example.
So pizza party is command line software to order pizza.
Why don't we take a look at the help on?
Okay, here we go.
Here is the syntax of pizza party.
Yep.
Program.
The options.
How many pizzas?
What size and what kind of crust?
All right, so let's take a look at the flags.
Here is username password for your dominoes account.
Input file, which allows you to order pizzas in batch if you're throwing a pizza party.
Vervose, quiet, and force, our typical command line arguments.
All right, standard Unix stuff.
Standard Unix stuff.
And here's some of the flags.
Onions, screen peppers, mushrooms, olives, tomatoes, pineapple.
Of course, if you haven't noticed yet, these are the toppings.
Cheddar cheese, pepperoni, sausage, ham, bacon, ground beef, grilled chicken, anchovies, and extra sauce.
So why don't we order a pizza?
Here you go.
What do you want on it?
Pepperoni?
Uh-huh.
Mushrooms?
Yep.
Anything else?
No, that's cool.
How many?
Just one.
Uh-huh.
What size?
Medium.
And what kind of crust?
Hmm, thin.
Thin crust.
Okay, here we go.
All right, so here's our confirmation.
1248 is your price.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
There you go.
All right.
And then it bumps us back to the command line.
You know, ready for fun stuff.
Yeah, so let's see what time it is.
All right, so 621.
So we'll see if the pizza comes in a half hour.
Oh, there we go.
See if the pizza comes in a half hour.
All right.
I'm hungry.
Hello.
There we go.
What do you guys want?
It comes to 1248.
Thank you.
How much more back to it, right?
1248.
Five up.
Oh, thin crust.
Oh, nice.
I never had.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, right?
It's good.
Yeah.